Finding Aid for the Jan Williams Collection of Images, 1962-2007
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Jan Williams Collection of Images, 1962-2007
Mus. Arc. 10.3
Williams, Jan, 1939-
4 boxes (548 items)
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
The Jan Williams Collection of Images contains images of various performances and trips made by Jan Williams with accompanying performers and composers. An original gift was received of 321 prints and contact sheets and 54 35mm slides in 2007. An additional gift was received of 173 photographs in 2008.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Jan Willams, 2007-2008
Accruals and Additions
No further accruals are expected to this collection.
Alternate Forms
Entire collection digitized and available in UB Libraries Digital Collections.
Biographical Note
Jan Williams was born in Utica, New York in 1939. He earned his B.M. and M.M. degrees as a percussionist at the Manhattan School of Music where he studied with Paul Price. Williams came to Buffalo as a Creative Associate at the Center of the Creative and Performing Arts in 1964. He became a member of the University at Buffalo Music Faculty in 1967 and Co-Director of the Center in 1974. Williams has been a mainstay of the international contemporary music scene, as percussionist, conductor, administrator, and educator.
Scope and Content Note
The Jan Williams Collection of Images consists of 548 photos, slides, and contact sheets, taken by Jan Williams, his friends, and professional photographers. The collection documents the career of Jan Williams and his travels to several countries, including Argentina, Brazil, Denmark, England, France, Germany, Italy, Poland, Spain, Uruguay, and many cities in the United States. More than one hundred images are of various venues in Buffalo, New York where Jan spent the bulk of his career. The collection contains images of many notable composers such as John Cage, Cornelius Cardew, Elliott Carter, David Del Tredici, Lukas Foss, Lejaren Hiller, Morton Feldman, Conlon Nancarrow, Pauline Oliveros, and Virgil Thomson. Performers represented in the images include the other members of the New Percussion Quartet, Creative Associates, Nils Vigeland, and Eberhard Blum.
Arrangement
The collection is divided into four series. Series I, II, and IV are prints of various sizes and Series III consists of 35mm slides.
I. Jan Williams alone.
II. Jan Williams and others.
III. Slides.
IV. Additional prints.
Container List
- Jan Williams alone, 1962-1987, I; Item 1-33
  Arranged in chronological order.
  - Jan Williams on television performing Lou Harrison's Canticle no. 3, 1962, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-001)
  - Diane Williams on television performing Lou Harrison's Canticle no. 3, 1962, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-002)
  - Jan Williams portrait sitting in the Creative Associates rehearsal room, old Baird Hall, percussion instruments in background, 1966, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-003)
  - Jan Williams portrait in the Creative Associates rehearsal room, old Baird Hall, 1966, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-004)
  - Jan Williams performing Luciano Berio's Circles at Evenings for New Music, 1967-02, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-005)
  - Jan Williams performing Elliott Carter's 8 Pieces for Four Timpani at the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1967-04, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-006)
  - Jan Williams at rehearsal for Kinder Koncert with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, 1970-03, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-007)
  - Jan Williams at S.E.M. rehearsal, 1970-03, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-008)
  - Jan Williams performing Lejaren Hiller's 3 Rituals for 2 Percussionists at Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1971-05, 1 photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 1, Item JW-009)
  - Jan Williams performing Lejaren Hiller's 3 Rituals for 2 Percussionists at Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1971-05, 1 photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 1, Item JW-010)
  - Jan Williams at the performance of Julius Eastman's Macle at the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1972-02, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-011)
  - Jan Williams playing percussion at old Baird Hall, undated, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-012)
  - Jan Williams conducting at Brock University, undated, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-013)
  - Jan Williams conducting, as printed on an advertisement for Evenings for New Music, with flutist Petr Kotík in foreground, undated, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-014)
  - Jan Williams at a rehearsal for Luciano Berio's Circles at the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1976-12, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-015)
  - Jan Williams portrait in hat and scarf, 1977, 1 photograph; Smit, Leo, 1921-1999 (Box 1, Item JW-016)
  - Jan Williams at a bar with beers, 1977, 1 photograph; Elmøe, Torben (Box 1, Item JW-017)
  - Jan Williams posing with marimba, undated, 1 photograph; Haupt, Irene (Box 1, Item JW-018)
  - Jan Williams playing with UB Percussion Ensemble (photo by Dave Gordon's father), 1982-02, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-019)
  - Jan Williams sitting, undated, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-020)
  - Jan Williams in Middelburg, Holland, 1985-07, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-021)
  - Black and white contact-sheet of 35 mm images of Jan Williams playing marimba, undated, 1 photograph; Harry, Don (Box 1, Item JW-022)
  - Jan Williams playing marimba and vibraphone in Slee Hall, undated, 1 photograph; Harry, Don (Box 1, Item JW-023)
  - Jan Williams playing marimba and vibraphone in Slee Hall, undated, 1 photograph; Harry, Don (Box 1, Item JW-024)
  - Jan Williams playing percussion in Miami, 1987-01, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-025)
  - Jan Williams playing percussion in Miami, 1987-01, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-026)
  - Jan Williams performing in Miami, 1987-01, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-027)
  - Jan Williams at home posing with gramophone that belonged to Diane Williams' grandparents, undated, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-028)
  - Jan Williams at home posing with gramophone that belonged to Diane Williams' grandparents, undated, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-029)
  - Jan Williams Solo Recital at Percussion Festival in Århus, Denmark, undated, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-030)
  - Jan Williams Solo Recital at Percussion Festival in Århus, Denmark, undated, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-031)
  - Jan Williams Solo Recital at Percussion Festival in Århus, Denmark, undated, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-032)
  - Jan Williams Solo Recital at Percussion Festival in Århus, Denmark, undated, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-033)
- Jan Williams and others, 1966-2007, II; Item 34-321
  - New Percussion Quartet posing with large frame, 1966, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-034)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing with statue, 1966, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-035)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing with large frame, 1966, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-036)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing with snare drum, 1966, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-037)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing with snare drum, 1966, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-038)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing with snare drum, 1966, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-039)
  - New Percussion Quartet playing snare drum, 1966, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-040)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing with hats, 1966, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-041)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing with sculpture, outdoors, 1966, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-042)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing with sculpture by Henry Moore, outdoors, 1966, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-043)
  - Margaret Krimsky-Hassell playing piano for a rehearsal of Be Prepared by the New Percussion Quartet, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-044)
  - Margaret Krimsky-Hassell playing piano for a rehearsal of Be Prepared by the New Percussion Quartet, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-045)
  - New Percussion Quartet with Margaret Krimsky-Hassel rehearsing Be Prepared, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-046)
  - New Percussion Quartet with Margaret Krimsky-Hassel rehearsing Be Prepared, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-047)
  - New Percussion Quartet with Margaret Krimsky-Hassel rehearsing Be Prepared, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-048)
  - New Percussion Quartet with Margaret Krimsky-Hassel rehearsing Be Prepared, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-049)
  - New Percussion Quartet with Margaret Krimsky-Hassel rehearsing Be Prepared, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-050)
  - New Percussion Quartet rehearsing in old Baird Hall, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-051)
  - New Percussion Quartet rehearsing in old Baird Hall, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-052)
  - New Percussion Quartet rehearsing in old Baird Hall, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-053)
  - New Percussion Quartet rehearsing in old Baird Hall, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-054)
  - New Percussion Quartet rehearsing in old Baird Hall, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-055)
  - New Percussion Quartet rehearsing in old Baird Hall, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-056)
  - New Percussion Quartet rehearsing in old Baird Hall, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-057)
  - New Percussion Quartet rehearsing in old Baird Hall, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-058)
  - New Percussion Quartet rehearsing in old Baird Hall, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-059)
  - New Percussion Quartet rehearsing in old Baird Hall, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-060)
  - New Percussion Quartet rehearsing in old Baird Hall, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-061)
  - New Percussion Quartet rehearsing in old Baird Hall, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-062)
  - New Percussion Quartet rehearsing in old Baird Hall, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-063)
  - New Percussion Quartet rehearsing in old Baird Hall, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-064)
  - New Percussion Quartet looking at a score of Paul Zonn's Tock, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-065)
  - New Percussion Quartet looking at a score of Paul Zonn's Tock, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-066)
  - New Percussion Quartet looking at a score of Paul Zonn's Tock, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-067)
  - Black and white contact-sheet of 35 mm images of New Percussion Quartet rehearsing in old Baird Hall, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-068)
  - Black and white contact-sheet of 35 mm images of New Percussion Quartet rehearsing in old Baird Hall and outdoors, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-069)
  - Black and white contact-sheet of 35 mm images of New Percussion Quartet looking at a score of Paul Zonn's Tock, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-070)
  - Black and white contact-sheet of 35 mm images of New Percussion Quartet rehearsing in old Baird Hall, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-071)
  - Black and white contact-sheet of 35 mm images of New Percussion Quartet rehearsing in old Baird Hall, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-072)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing outside of old Baird Hall with umbrellas, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-073)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing outside of old Baird Hall, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-074)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing outside of old Baird Hall, 1967-08, 1 photograph; Dawson, Bob (Box 1, Item JW-075)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing by windows in the auditorium of the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-076)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing by windows in the auditorium of the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, with drum, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-077)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing by windows in the auditorium of the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, with drum, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-078)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing by windows in the auditorium of the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-079)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing outdoors at Albright-Knox Art Gallery, with snare drum, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-080)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing outdoors at Albright-Knox Art Gallery, each with snare drums, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-081)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing outdoors at Albright-Knox Art Gallery, with sculpture, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-082)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing outdoors at Albright-Knox Art Gallery, with sculpture and snare drum, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-083)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing outdoors at Albright-Knox Art Gallery, with sculpture, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-084)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing with sculpture by Jean Arp at the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-085)
  - New Percussion Quartet posing in front of Toccata and Fugue by Jan Arman at the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-086)
  - New Percussion Quartet on stairs of Albright-Knox Art Gallery with snare drums, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-087)
  - New Percussion Quartet at Albright-Knox Art Gallery with drums, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-088)
  - New Percussion Quartet at Albright-Knox Art Gallery with percussion instruments, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-089)
  - New Percussion Quartet at Albright-Knox Art Gallery with percussion instruments, 1967, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-090)
  - Jan Williams and Edward Burnham performing Ben Johnston's Knocking Piece at the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1967-11, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-091)
  - New Percussion Quartet performing at a grade school in Buffalo, 1968, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-092)
  - New Percussion Quartet performing at a grade school in Buffalo, 1968, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-093)
  - New Percussion Quartet performing at a grade school in Buffalo, 1968, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-094)
  - New Percussion Quartet performing at a grade school with student playing bass drum, 1968, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-095)
  - New Percussion Quartet performing at a grade school with student playing bass drum, 1968, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-096)
  - New Percussion Quartet performing David Rosenboom's To That Predestined Dancing Place at old Baird Hall, 1968-01, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-097)
  - New Percussion Quartet performing John Cage's She Is Asleep at old Baird Hall, 1968-01, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-098)
  - New Percussion Quartet performing David Rosenboom's To That Predestined Dancing Place at old Baird Hall, 1968-01, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-099)
  - New Percussion Quartet performing Michael Colgrass' Inventions on a Motive at old Baird Hall for 2nd Festival of the Arts, Melvin Strauss conducting, 1968-01, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JW-100)
  - New Percussion Quartet performing Bill Russell's Three Dance Movements at old Baird Hall for 2nd Festival of the Arts, 1968-03, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-101)
  - New Percussion Quartet performing John Bergamo's Interactions for Vibe and Percussion Ensemble at old Baird Hall for 2nd Festival of the Arts, 1968-03, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-102)
  - New Percussion Quartet performing Lou Harrison's Fugue at old Baird Hall for 2nd Festival of the Arts, 1968-03, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-103)
  - John Cage performing his Amores with the New Percussion Quartet at the Albright-Knox Art Gallery for the 2nd Festival of the Arts, 1968-03, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-104)
  - David Rosenboom with the New Percussion Quartet at an Albright-Knox Art Gallery performance for the 2nd Festival of the Arts, 1968-03, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-105)
  - John Cage with toy gun during performance of David Rosenboom's To That Predestined Dancing Place at Albright-Knox Art Gallery performance for the 2nd Festival of the Arts, 1968-03, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-106)
  - John Cage and unidentified girl performing his She Is Asleep at Albright-Knox Art Gallery performance for the 2nd Festival of the Arts, 1968-03, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-107)
  - New Percussion Quartet performing William Kraft's Concerto for Percussion and Orchestra with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, 1969-01, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-108)
  - New Percussion Quartet performing William Kraft's Concerto for Percussion and Orchestra with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, 1969-01, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-109)
  - New Percussion Quartet performing William Kraft's Concerto for Percussion and Orchestra with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, 1969-01, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-110)
  - New Percussion Quartet performing William Kraft's Concerto for Percussion and Orchestra with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, 1969-01, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-111)
  - New Percussion Quartet performing William Kraft's Concerto for Percussion and Orchestra with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, 1969-01, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-112)
  - New Percussion Quartet performing William Kraft's Concerto for Percussion and Orchestra with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, 1969-01, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-113)
  - New Percussion Quartet performing William Kraft's Concerto for Percussion and Orchestra with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, 1969-01, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item JW-114)
  - Creative Associates at performance of Klaus von Wrochem's Stücke, 1967-03, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item JW-115)
  - Jan Williams and Ed Burnham performing William Albright's composition for 2 drummers, film, and tape at Hallwalls, Essex St., 1967-04, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-116)
  - Jan Williams and Ed Burnham performing Stockhausen's Plus-Minus during Evenings for New Music with Cornelius Cardew at the piano, 1967-04, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item JW-117)
  - Jan Williams and Ed Burnham performing Stockhausen's Plus-Minus during Evenings for New Music with Cornelius Cardew at the piano, 1967-04, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item JW-118)
  - Performance of Lukas Foss' Paradigm at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 photograph; Robert, Jacques (Box 2, Item JW-119)
  - Jan Williams bowing with Lukas Foss after a performance of Lukas Foss' Paradigm at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 photograph; Robert, Jacques (Box 2, Item JW-120)
  - Jan Williams and others practicing before a performance of Lukas Foss' MAP at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 photograph; Robert, Jacques (Box 2, Item JW-121)
  - Jan Williams bowing at a performance of his Dream Lesson at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 photograph; Robert, Jacques (Box 2, Item JW-122)
  - Jan Williams and Ed Yadzinski performing Jan Williams' Dream Lesson at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 photograph; Robert, Jacques (Box 2, Item JW-123)
  - Images from performance of Jan Williams' Dream Lesson at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 photograph; Robert, Jacques (Box 2, Item JW-124)
  - Jan Williams painting at Nuits de la Foundation Maeght at St. Paul de Vence, 1970-07, 1 photograph; Robert, Jacques (Box 2, Item JW-125)
  - Jan Williams conducting at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 photograph; Robert, Jacques (Box 2, Item JW-126)
  - Jan Williams conducting at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 photograph; Robert, Jacques (Box 2, Item JW-127)
  - Jan Williams at the piano at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 photograph; Robert, Jacques (Box 2, Item JW-128)
  - Jan Williams playing a musical saw at theNuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 photograph; Robert, Jacques (Box 2, Item JW-129)
  - Jan Williams, in hat, playing double bass at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 photograph; Robert, Jacques (Box 2, Item JW-130)
  - Jan Williams and Renée Levine, 1970, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-131)
  - UB Percussion Ensemble Performance, 1970, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-132)
  - UB Percussion Ensemble group photo, 1971, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-133)
  - UB Percussion Ensemble with Mark Sokol performing Lou Harrison's Concerto for violin and percussion, 1971-02, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-134)
  - Jan Williams and friends in Buffalo, 1971-09, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-135)
  - S.E.M. Ensemble, 1972, 1 photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item JW-136)
  - Jan Williams and Luis De Pablo discussing De Pablo's Le Prie dieu sur le terrasse in old Baird Room 100, 1974, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-137)
  - Jan Williams rehearsing Luis De Pablo's Le Prie dieu sur le terrasse in old Baird Room 100, 1974, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-138)
  - Jan Williams and Luis De Pablo rehearsing Luis De Pablo's Le Prie dieu sur le terrasse in old Baird Room 100, 1974, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-139)
  - Jan Williams and Luis De Pablo rehearsing Luis De Pablo's Le Prie dieu sur le terrasse in Baird Room 100, 1974, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-140)
  - Members of the Center of the Creative and Performing Arts at the Albright-Knox Art Gallery front steps, 1975, 1 photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 2, Item JW-141)
  - Jan Williams, Joan La Barbara, and Nora Post at a rehearsal at Albright-Knox Art Gallery Auditorium, 1977-02, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-142)
  - Nils Vigeland, Morton Feldman, Jan Williams, and Eberhard Blum outside a door in London, 1977, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-143)
  - Jan Williams and Fuzzy performing Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra with the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-144)
  - Jan Williams rehearsing Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra for performance with the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra (conductor Richard Dufallo in background), 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-145)
  - Jan Williams (barely visible) on stage with percussion set up for a performance of Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra with the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-146)